Joni Lai

Senior Blockchain Developer

Senior Blockchain & Web Developer specializing in blockchain development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for Cosmos blockchain: airdrop, presale, staking, custom token and NFT. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including **Solidity**, **Rust**, C/C++, Qt, Node.js, React, Next.js, GraphQL and MySQL. Especially well-versed in Interchain technology based on CosmosSDK.



- phantomtop0127@gmail.com
- Singapore, Singapore
- twitter.com/Joni_Lai
- github.com/PhantomTop

- 1 940 220 9574
- doodleworkshop.web.app
- S live:.cid.ea6edcba6e753852
- stackoverflow.com/users/17933073/phantom-top

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Atos Information Technology

01/2012 - 03/2017

Singapore

Blockchain Developer

LANEXUS

06/2017 - 10/2021 Philippines

Blockchain Developer/CTO

FortisOeconomia

02/2022 - 05/2022 Turkey

Blockchain Developer

MarbleDAO

02/2022 - Present Swiss

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Nanyang Technological University

09/2008 - 05/2012

SKILLS

Blockchain Technology

MERN Stack

C/C++

Java

Rust

Solidity

Qt/QML

MySQL

GraphQL

PERSONAL PROJECTS

https://doodleworkshop.web.app (12/2021 - 02/2022)

https://junocoinflip.web.app (06/2022 - 07/2022)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Great skill on Cosmwasm (11/2021 - Present)

Recently, I've built some more marvelous products on **Juno** such as presale, airdrop, staking, custom token, bot and NFT. Mastered with **GraphQL**, I also have built blockchain analyzer products using **graph-node** and **subgraph**. **Able to make new Blockchain** based on cosmosSDK and **DApps** and services running on it.

LANGUAGES

Enalish

Professional Working Proficiency

Malay

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Reading

Pingpong